Hey, welcome back.
Uh, I think I may just go back to the beginning.
Now that I have this teleport option.
I wanted to go there anyway.
Just because I needed to... Well, see the stuff I was given in the very beginning of this place, right?
Yeah.
I also definitely missed some paths here.
Like that one.
Wait, did I actually go that way?
I think I may have.
This one I solved, I believe.
Warriors don't like death.
Death loves warriors.
Yeah.
Now out here... Right.
The duty.
Let me see that again.
Warriors, stop!
Warriors, go.
Yeah.
The duty.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wall slash fortification.
This is the symbol that was shown when they were building the wall.
Could mean fortress.
Yeah, let's just keep it as this.
This is pretty good.
Now, notice that these guys have swords and helmets.
I could most likely get down there with the disguise.
Speak enough.
My disguise is gone.
What if I go up here now?
This just takes me where exactly?
Right.
This is the very start.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
What if I go left?
And then down.
Are they gonna see me?
Maybe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Run!
I don't know where I'm running.
Just run, run.
Oh, I'm fucked.
Oh, no.
Oh, it is what it is.
Okay, then.
But interesting that this place right here, as soon as you enter, then we have the wall slash fortification.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm gonna follow in my footsteps here.
If I missed anything else.
I don't think I did.
Get over here now.
And up there.
Right.
Duty.
The warrior carries the duty.
And then I kind of need to see these again because they were kind of hard to see before.
So this guy is saying the same thing here.
Warrior stop.
Warriors go.
Or move.
Like the pictures that I have in my book are nice, but it's kind of hard to see what's going on.
I want to take another look at these.
I think it's intriguing.
Yeah, this way.
And then up here.
Yeah.
Get on the old hamster wheel.
Such an odd mechanism.
Really weird.
I wonder if this symbolizes something.
Okay.
So what's happening here in this picture?
These guys down here.
Oh, they're definitely the demons.
Right?
Yeah, the warrior pushes back the impure.
Exactly.
Right.
Okay.
Let me see the last one again.
I can't believe it took me that long to realize that those creatures in front were not just humans.
They did look weird.
I did think about that back then, but you know.
And this one is, we protect the chosen ones.
Yeah, the warrior protects the chosen, pushes back the evil, and does his duty, right?
That is the duty.
Super cool.
Yep.
Okay, so I'm also missing this guy.
Someone ringing the bell.
What could that signify?
This looks like a special kind of warrior, doesn't it?
Then again, not really.
They kind of look similar.
Now, I may be wrong in thinking that it has to be associated with what we're seeing here.
I mean, this is the moon.
No doubt about it.
This is the sun.
No doubt about that or God.
Those things are synonymous here in this world, it seems.
And the bell could represent music?
Could this guy be the astronomer?
It's related to this, right?
Actually, yeah, think about this.
The dude living in that shack out in the middle of nowhere.
What did he have next to his house?
A bunch of bells.
He was ringing the bell.
Right?
He loves bottles.
What is he doing up there on the roof?
He's watching the night sky.
This is him.
Oh my God, I'm wrong?
I was so sure of that.
God damn it.
Okay, never mind then.
Okay.
I'm really surprised that I am wrong about that.
But I guess if you're wrong, you're wrong.
There's not much else to say there.
This game does humble you sometimes.
Okay, so I don't have a disguise now.
Wait, do I?
Oh, my disguise is back.
That's convenient.
Weapons.
I could go back up there, I guess.
Yeah, let's go back up there.
Oh, oh, oh.
If I get too close, they start to get suspicious.
They're gonna see through my disguise.
Okay, here we go.
Weapons.
There must be something out here I may have missed.
Probably.
What was up here again?
Right, this place.
The warrior's duty.
Carry the weapon, push back the impure, and protect the chosen ones.
Push the impure.
Yeah,
protect the chosen.
Yeah, beautiful.
Okay, I guess I have nowhere else to go but up here.
Hmm.
Now, there were these chambers over here that I did not know.
Yeah.
Oh, wait a minute.
The chosen ones are up here.
No, shit.
I guess that makes sense.
They are higher up.
The angels are obviously closer to the sky, right?
The warriors stop.
Oh, interesting.
So this is that symbol we saw with the ship and the mural.
Warriors stop.
The warriors stopped.
Hmm.
Ship stars god.
Maybe the warriors arrived at the chosen ones.
You know?
The warriors stopped their ship when they came upon the chosen ones.
And then the impure prevent death.
No, wait, that doesn't make sense.
The impure cause death?
What do the impure do?
The demons bring death.
Something that would make sense in the context of stop and halt.
Which is something I guessed over here but I could be wrong about this one, right?
Whatever this word is should reflect what's going on in this image and also in the context of this sentence.
The demons something death.
What do the demons do with death?
The demons bring death.
But bring, does that make sense up here?
No, this is definitely halt.
But that is counterintuitive to me.
I would imagine the demons, well, you know, causing death, not stopping death.
What else could this mean?
Warriors stop.
Warriors halt.
Pause.
Stand still.
Hmm.
This one is so confusing.
What does that mean?
No idea.
This game is a real brain twister.
You really got to think here.
Also, I don't think I'm very good at the languages here at deciphering this stuff.
I'm definitely more mathematically inclined than linguistically.
That's for sure.
Let's see what we have over here again.
So, if this is saying this area is for the chosen ones, I'm imagining that this guy up here, who I thought was an astronomer, is actually a chosen one.
Except he doesn't really look like one, does he?
Ah, never mind.
I thought this was the same image as this one.
But it's not.
It's different.
Okay, then.
Well, in that case, then it's this one.
Yeah.
The bell ringer?
Bellman.
Okay.
That's very precise, I guess.
Straightforward.
Sun and moon, alright.
Cool.
Very good.
The bellman.
Bellman loves the bottle.
He sure does.
Let's head back in here.
Now that he's busy with the bottle, I can take another look here.
Okay.
So, if there's a duty as the second word, what would be the first word?
Duty of... something.
We know none of these.
That's crazy.
Oh, wait a minute.
Duty?
Sun?
Chosen?
Wait
a minute now.
Whatever this first word is, it's the same in all of these.
And it's also the glyph that we saw in the mural, right?
And it comes first in all of these.
Which was like a journey.
But what could that mean?
Travel?
Travel, ship, stars, god, I don't know.
Journey.
It's probably the most sensible one.
But that doesn't make sense to say journey, son.
Hmm.
This guy right here is very important right now.
Also, these symbols look nothing like what we see here.
In this language.
This looks like a new language.
Am I crazy?
Never mind, I'm crazy.
It's the exact same.
Look.
Scratch that from the record.
I gotta go to the mural again.
Gotta have another look at that.
Did I really not take a...
...note on that mural?
Damn, I didn't.
If only I could figure this out.
One guy becomes many guys?
Multiplication?
Having kids?
Group versus individual?
Oh, wait a minute.
Plural.
Oh!
Of course!
Wait!
Huh?
Go pass?
I'm so good.
Plural, yes!
Of course!
Wow, alright, alright, alright, alright.
That's huge.
But that didn't reveal anything new in here, I don't think.
But it's one step closer to the truth.
Yeah.
At least plural is confirmed now, right?
I mean, we knew that already, but... That one was pretty much confirmed already.
Alright, Bellman, I'll be back later.
I mean, I could just guess the order here, you know?
There's four bells, meaning four factorial combinations.
I'm not gonna do that, though.
The ship here, this represents the chosen ones, I think, because of the music, right?
Let's have another look in the book and see if any of the other glyphs here appear.
Here's a shield, a harp,
boxes and bottles,
scales of justice, the key.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I think this maybe represents the warriors, because they arrived by ship, right?
This represents God, because God looks at instruments, remember that, from the first area?
The other two, I'm not so sure about.
But we definitely need more information for this.
Let's quickly review what we're missing in here.
Did I actually get everything so far?
The warrior protects the chosen, pushes back the impure and carries the duty.
Yeah, I got everything so far.
That's mind-blowing.
I want to go check out the big sword now that we have some new words.
That should make things a little more clear, I think.
Chosen once, yeah.
Okay, now this one,
the warrior carries a weapon, CC.
Now this one,
warrior not, fear death, probably wrong with fear.
Warrior not cause death.
And what about this one?
This is the chosen one.
Chosen carry, possess a instrument.
That one is instrument.
Okay, that's huge.
Definitely an instrument.
Instrument of music.
Maybe, let me think, there's skull, he's walking on skulls.
Dead people.
Let me see this again.
Warrior not fear death.
I think fear is wrong.
What else could it be?
Warrior does not...
trample death, does not...
I mean, I would say skulls.
If you're walking on skulls like that so proudly like he's doing here, I think that could mean warrior does not fear death, you know?
He walks on these skulls like it's nothing.
He's not afraid of death.
Skulls represent death, right?
Okay, guys, what are you saying now?
Warriors
wait...
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Warriors wait...
for the journey of the chosen ones?
I think I may need to change my gear to look like these dudes.
They have a shield and a thingy.
I'll be back.
I want to look at that mural one more time, and after that I'm going to go change my gear to the spear.
But then I have to be careful on the way here.
Hopefully, nobody's going to notice me, right?
It almost seems like there's different ranks within these warriors.
We have the guys like me right now, with the sword and the bracers.
And then we have the spear masters.
Seems like a higher rank, doesn't it?
Simply because they're higher up, literally, in the city.
I'm going to call this city Sanara, because I think that's what it is.
What else could it be, right?
Okay, let's see here.
Yeah, this is the same thing.
The impure ones await death.
Okay.
Maybe this also means await.
The warriors await...
the meeting, perhaps, or the...
encounter with the chosen ones.
Weapons, chosen ones.
Where was the way to...
to the mural?
Was it here?
Ah, look, astronomer.
That one is definitely not correct.
Now these guys...
What are you saying now, sir?
Yes.
The impure ones await death.
Oh, let me guess, he's saying, and he's waiting for a bottle.
And then they laugh.
Bellman awaits the bottle.
Ah, I see.
Okay, and then they laugh.
Okay, that makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, I get it now.
All right.
I gave the Bellman a bottle already.
I don't think I need to go back up there.
I need to go the other way here.
Oh, what's this over here?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is this?
An elevator.
What?
How do I operate this guy?
Not to mention, what is this place over here?
Astronomer.
I mean, I got this one wrong for sure.
Oh, I have to go with these guys again, I think.
There's no other way.
I got to go through the motions.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
I can talk to this guy?
Oh, okay.
He's just saying no.
Okay, we got to go through this one again.
I wonder if the order is going to be different this time.
Man, I'm really hoping this is the way to the mural.
Because I don't quite remember.
There's so many paths here.
Okay, I think I'm going to take the bottle now again.
Okay, okay, okay.
I got you.
Little crate.
See, see.
Warriors march.
Okay, okay, march.
See, that makes sense, right?
It's a context thing.
Like, it is go slash pass, but in the context of this drill sergeant, it's march.
March and halt.
Warrior march.
March on out of there.
Okay.
And I'll be the one pushing again.
I got you.
This time I'm not running, it seems.
I'm just walking normally.
They love their crates, their bottles, and their carts, you know?
They also had carts in the first level of the tower.
Can I go this?
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay, okay, don't screw it up now.
Okay, yeah, here we are.
So...
Man, what else could this mean?
Stars in the night sky.
There's this chosen one power up on top of the tower.
And he's like, look, there it is, pointing to it.
The rest are like, whoa, sick, let's go there.
They love it.
Notice also the shape of this thing.
Looks a lot like the ship itself.
You see that?
It's got to be the ship.
Except the conversations don't make sense with the ship.
Yeah, that is a mystery.
That is a big mystery.
Notice also how this writing isn't blue.
This writing is in this color, does that matter?
Let's see the other ones.
It's blue now again, and then red.
And then sort of brown.
Ah, actually, yeah, okay, brown.
Hmm.
The warriors built.
Maybe they just built their whole city.
You know, the place that we saw when we first entered.
Maybe their headquarters or garrison.
Yeah.
This looks like a ship, I mean, if you think of the shape here.
Actually, now that I look at this, it doesn't quite look like that shape, does it?
Maybe a bit.
Not that much, it would have to be like that straight.
I mean...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Ship stars, it's blue.
The stars are blue.
Nah, I don't know.
I just don't know about this one, to be honest.
I think it's time to go back to the bellman.
And just try a combination.
So, we do have the book, right?
That is on his table.
And it did list those things in a given order, so maybe that order is the order I need to put it in, but it seems a little too simple, doesn't it?
I was expecting there to be maybe a deeper puzzle behind that, and maybe there is.
But I'm gonna try it anyway, and who knows, maybe I'll have a revelation.
Now, this right here...
has got to be a clue.
Right?
Let's grab this torch again.
Like, come on, there's gotta be something here.
Maybe these circles on the wall will do something.
You gotta be kidding me, there's gotta be...
Put this down here.
Look at this one now, maybe the shadows will tell a story.
No.
The scales of justice.
This could represent...
The warriors dealing with the impure, you know, dealing out justice.
The ship...
Well, represents the ship, I guess.
Again, with the very specific shape of the sail.
We got the music and the key.
Perhaps there's a combination here where you put this down in a specific order.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Ship comes first.
How about I don't have an option to activate that first?
This is a real mystery.
Look at this here in the center, there's something going on with that.
Get back inside of here, please.
Oh, look at the stars emanating.
Wait a second, there's small holes in these screens.
You're seeing this?
Oh, that's weird.
Okay.
If only I could put down the torch inside of here somehow.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight dots, four dots, three, six dots.
There's no way that has any meaning though, right?
Because it's so reliant on me being precise.
Man.
That's weird.
Can I take the torch with me?
Oh yeah, I can, I guess.
Now, this thing needed something that I couldn't quite figure out.
Hold on, does this sound different every time I do this?
Ah, no, it's the same.
Man, I have no clue what's happening here.
This torch is the equivalent of that card game I played on the first level of the tower.
Initially, I had no idea what was going on and it's the same here.
I have literally no idea.
So, okay.
The fact that I'm walking around with this light in my hand, could that just simply suggest this?
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
These things on the wall look like stars now when you're in here.
Maybe it's simply a clue that this means stars.
Starlight.
I mean, it's a frickin' prism with light refracting through it.
Um...
Starlight.
I mean, it's a goddamn prism, right?
Light comes in from the stars, it gets refracted, and because starlight consists of many different colors of light or wavelengths of light, they all get refracted by different amounts, right?
That's how you separate out all the different wavelengths.
In fact, that's how we know what things are made of in the universe.
We look at the light and we see what wavelengths of light are there.
Can I do anything here?
I don't think so.
Let's try and bring the torch with us the other way.
Light, take this torch and take it with us all the way back here.
If we can.
We can't.
Okay.
Damn.
Man, I don't know.
So obviously, whatever's going on down here is related to the bells.
Because the bells have the same symbols.
They have the same symbols.
Maybe it is simply about counting the dots.
Let's try and do this, actually.
But these two are kind of hard to reach with the dots.
We only have a screen here, here, here, and here, and...
It's almost like I need to rotate this...
frame here, because you see the shape of this room?
It's the opposite of the shape of this thing.
Is that the thing I can rotate downstairs?
I think for sure it is.
Wait, can I go on the other side and do something?
Hold on.
Put this down.
You're kidding!
Motherfucker!
Unbelievable!
Wow!
Okay.
Yeah, I knew it.
I frickin' knew it!
Okay, okay.
Now, I didn't quite calculate how much to rotate this, but...
So that would be...
Two more, I think?
Like that?
Here we go.
Yes!
Oh my god, let's see.
See, now I can put it down?
Unbelievable.
Ha ha ha!
Okay.
The fact that you couldn't operate the thing while holding it...
I feel like they could have telegraphed that a little better.
I thought it meant I needed some other item that I didn't have, because that's the universal sign.
When he shrugs his shoulders, being like, I can't do that.
You know?
So I thought I needed to go grab some kind of pry bar.
Or something else.
Okay, so what do we have here?
Treasure?
Cenar?
The city?
No, actually, this is the fortification they built.
It's that.
This is a crate?
But filled with riches, which makes it a treasure chest.
And someone is yelling or singing.
Not sure about that one, but let's take a look here.
Oh my goodness!
Is that the ship they came in?
Or one of them?
And these are the treasures?
This is the treasure room.
Wow!
Look at all this!
Can't do anything with that.
Okay.
Oh, that is funny.
Let's see here.
Viking helmet or something?
An axe?
Is that what I think it is?
Is that the thing that needed to go on the telescope?
No, that one was more roundish.
Okay, before I do anything here, I can also operate this to go up and down, it seems.
But let's just take a moment and calm down.
What's going on over here?
Oh, this is the dude from the zoom call.
The detective.
Wow, we got three new ones?
Astronomer.
Look, he's looking through a, well, what do you call this thing?
A magnifying glass.
You know, he's studying the sky.
A researcher.
Oh, these are the things I got.
Someone searches something.
To help.
This is the astronomer.
Look, we got devotees in the back.
Devotee and soldiers.
Okay, to help.
So this means searches.
Search.
And this one is help.
Weirdly enough, this looks like a chest.
If you rotate this 45 degrees to the right.
It looks like a crate.
The astronomer, I think this may be a sign for the astronomer.
Or detective.
Yeah, the astronomer slash detective searches.
Searches.
Searches something that we can't see.
To help.
To help the soldiers.
Or the devotees, or both of them combined.
Interesting.
To help.
Who else could this mean?
No, it has to be this guy, whoever that is, right?
I mean, look at the way he's dressed.
He looks like a detective.
And that's literally what astronomers are, right?
We're just detectives of the cosmos.
We're trying to put things together, you know?
It's a big old mystery that needs to be solved.
And we're getting clues through starlight.
Searches.
The stars.
This symbol is stars for sure.
Man, that is cool.
Oh, we're noting down things?
Look at this dude.
His eyes are literally the symbol of help.
Like this.
Could also represent glasses in a way.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so, oh, I didn't even need to have this here.
I already know this.
This is help.
And this is seek.
Or search.
This is the astronomer.
I can't wait to see what they're calling him.
Scientist.
Okay, well, close enough.
Yeah, awesome.
Okay, okay.
Very nice.
It's weirdly futuristic looking in here, though.
Compared to all the wooden stuff, right?
Okay, so, wait a sec here.
The scientist had a...
What do you call it?
A zoom thingy.
Maybe I can find that here?
I don't know which ones to pick here.
Let me try and go up.
Does nothing.
Oh, of course, I gotta go into hamster wheel.
And look, I can even adjust the level I see now.
Well, I don't know what to go for yet.
So...
Not sure.
Now, down here, we do have some things on display.
A horn, a helmet, a necklace, and a goblet.
Perhaps I need to grab those things?
So, a horn...
Ah, look at this musical instrument.
It's exactly like the picture.
Let's do the horn.
Third level.
Okay, one, two, three, four, five.
And there's one, two, three, four, five, six here.
So, that means...
It needs to go one...
Oh, I fucked up.
I fucked up.
It's okay.
I can grab the one from the next level.
The necklace.
Oh, never mind.
I am on the right one.
Okay.
Perfect.
Now, how do I...
Shit.
Oh, I'm a dumbass.
I see now.
Wait, is that not the necklace right there?
Am I crazy?
Yeah, it is, look.
But this is not what I'm supposed to do.
I need to find the right one here, I guess.
Which one would it be?
Let me take a look at the book again.
Can I find the thing that goes on the telescope?
Could it be that one?
It could be that one.
It kind of looks like it, doesn't it?
Or even that one?
Ah, I clicked on that already, though.
Yeah.
Let's try and grab this one.
I have a feeling.
Put it, I guess, here.
And now we gotta go up.
One...
One, two, three, four, five.
All the way to the top.
Four and five.
Yeah.
But what about the top one, then?
Is that not possible to get?
Don't tell me I'm going too far now.
Damn it!
Ah, that's painful, dude!
Oh, I suck!
What am I doing?
That is painful.
We gotta go to four.
One more.
There it is.
Okay, okay.
Give me that thing.
Yes!
Yep.
Oh, look at this!
It's going to point out constellations on the sky, I guarantee it.
Those lines definitely are going to be connected by the stars.
That's neat.
Also, we gotta take another look at the light projection room.
Because I did not count the stars.
Let's see.
How many stars does this one have?
One, two, three, four, five, six.
They're also in a specific pattern.
Okay, and we have the boat.
Oh, we're going to note it down!
Okay, okay, good.
Very good.
Let's see if we can do this.
So, ship.
I think this is ship.
This is musical instrument.
There.
Scales?
Justice?
That could be the whole pushing back the demons.
Okay, I'm not sure what that one is then.
These two I'm unsure of.
Wait, is this literally...
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two...
No.
Do I have something that looks like this?
That one.
You see the amount of points?
One, two, three points.
Four, five, six.
We technically also have two in the center here.
Well, you could argue maybe not.
Because they're crossing.
I mean, it's not like a vertex, right?
It's like a crossing.
Intersection, of course, is what they're called.
This one has one, two, three, four, five, six.
And it goes sort of like that.
Oh, that's...
Oh, it even looks like a key!
Look at that shit!
Oh my god, I figured it out.
This one is wrong, of course.
So let's see here.
Something that goes down like that.
Oh, it's this guy!
Yes!
Oh, that's beautiful!
They actually look like the things they represent.
Balance.
Right.
Key.
Vessel.
All right!
But!
This was not the symbol that was on the mural.
The symbol on the mural next to the ship...
was this guy.
So, what's going on there?
Right?
Also, I did not count...
Oh, but I guess we have them in the journal now.
Uh, am I going the right way?
Let me think.
Uh...
Probably.
Yeah, go up here.
We have this thing now.
We gotta go back to the telescope.
I'm getting excited!
Uh, but can I exit here with no issues?
Are they going to be mad at me?
Hopefully not.
Don't mind me, guys.
I'll get back in line as quickly as I can.
I just have to take a quick toilet break.
You know how it is.
There we go.
All right.
Um...
Oh, but...
I don't have a sword!
No!
Fuck!
I forgot about it.
I forgot about the no-sword situation.
Stupid.
What am I doing?
Let's try this once more.
Crazy, though, that they would just chase me like that.
What if I had just forgotten the sword on the john, you know?
They were just going to go up there and kill me?
Thank you.
All right, I'm off again.
Let's go visit the scientist headquarters.
Which is...
Ooh, I forgot...
Was it up here?
Uh...
Yeah, this one led to the telescope, I think.
Yeah, perfect.
Take me up through that door.
Man, I love these vistas.
These panoramas here are amazing.
Yes.
Oh, it just all occurred to me as well.
Look at the thing on the paper.
That's exactly the thing I was looking for.
The reason I hesitated in the room with all the treasures...
is that the thing on the telescope itself looks way more round in shape.
You see this?
Actually, never mind.
It does sort of look like a star.
I just... I got bamboozled by the inner square.
Yeah, never mind.
Yeah!
Show me the constellations, baby.
Let's have a look.
I mean...
It's telling me what I already knew.
So clever, though, that the glyphs themselves...
look like the things that the glyphs represent.
Hahaha!
It's like right there in your face!
I swear to God, sometimes with these puzzle games, I cannot see the forest for the trees.
It's like one of my biggest, uh...
you know, whatever.
Well...
Oh, we got notes now.
Oh, okay.
Beautiful drawing there.
Look at me nailing everything, except this one.
Treasure?
Uh...
What could this represent?
Fear?
Yelling?
Shouting?
Yeah.
This is definitely fortification.
Treasure could represent all kinds of different objects, right?
Would it make sense for this to be treasure?
On the mural, it represented the ship...
and then pointing out...
Ahh!
I think it would represent treasure.
The guy's like, look!
He's pointing his finger, right?
Look, guys!
There's a huge temple in the distance!
We gotta go rob it!
That's why they came there in the first place, right?
They saw treasure on the horizon.
And then they realized when they arrived there that they got enchanted by the music.
And they really liked it, so they decided to stay.
And protect the people living there and push back the evil.
The warriors don't fear death.
Now, these two I'm not so sure about, but I think this is correct.
Never mind.
Okay.
I feel like this could represent fear...
but I guess not.
Someone's shouting...
a hooded figure...
That one I'm not sure about.
But let's go back to the... to the bellman.
Now, where was the bellman again?
I think he was quite close to...
Oh, what was that spot?
I'll know it when I see it.
Yeah.
When he walks down these stairs, it looks so silly.
Okay, so I think it's down here and up.
Or down, actually.
Because I came from here just now.
And over here, there was an elevator.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, why is it here?
What the hell?
What is this?
What?
A nice little shortcut.
No, shit, okay.
Well, that's good to know.
So, the scientist is communicating with the soldiers...
and the devotees, or the humans, on the first level as well.
Because, via the Zoom call, he was speaking to both of them, right?
Unless I'm completely misremembering this.
Starlight, this one is probably wrong.
Um...
It is not through here.
It is...
That means it's not here either.
It's north.
Gah!
I cannot find my way.
Hey, lizard.
Now, did I get this whole thing ready yet?
Warriors wait.
Shipstar's god.
The warriors wait for treasure?
No, that doesn't make sense.
Actually...
Yeah, I don't think this is treasure.
I may be wrong about that, in fact.
This could be fear.
By the way, the fear was totally...
just pulled out of my ass, so that could be totally wrong.
Here we go, chosen ones.
Oh, also, we may need to change our gear.
But let's start with the...
the dude up here.
The...
the bellman.
Yeah, see if we can't figure this out now.
We have the constellations.
I think it's all about counting the stars.
That would make sense to me.
Let's see here now.
Oh, one more thing.
Let's check the book once more.
Yeah, this is the one glyph I cannot figure out, man.
It really, really is.
What could it be?
What could that glyph be?
I cannot even start to understand that.
Okay, let's see.
Look at the book.
One, two, three, four...
five, six on the key.
One, two, three, four, five...
six, seven...
on whatever that was.
The ship.
No, this was...
Yeah, this was the ship.
Yeah, ship key.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Uh-oh.
One, two, three... Oh, no.
Oh, I don't know the order.
Let's just think logically.
The scales definitely represent the last part of the mural.
I think.
The ship is the first part?
Ah, man, I don't know.
That is rough.
I don't have the faintest.
Let's see.
Will solving this help me?
Maybe.
Yeah, actually, it probably would.
Treasure?
I mean, this is obviously treasure.
This is...
could be a siren.
Someone who enchants sailors.
Right?
The sailors are coming?
They're being enchanted by the music?
A siren?
That actually makes a lot of sense.
The soldiers who were so intent on getting treasure...
Right?
We saw their treasure room.
The only way for them to sort of change their ways is to...
become enchanted by a siren.
Now, this one, there's sun rays shining here.
But no, this is definitely the fortification.
There's no doubt about it.
We are missing how many?
Four more other than that.
Am I missing two somewhere?
No, I got them all.
So I think it's a skill issue right now.
I cannot figure out this puzzle.
I mean, the puzzle of this...
So this... Is it just the order?
Ship first, scale, harp, key?
What is the order here?
It's different.
Let's just try this order.
Ship, scale, harp, key.
Wait, what am I doing?
Ship, scale, harp...
Oh, wait a second now!
Hold the fucking phone, there's five here!
One, two, three, four... Wait, what?!
Wait, wait a minute!
What's happening?
Why are there five bells?
Huh?
Oh, that is confusing.
Let's take a look at this again.
That, I... I have no clue.
Is this referring to the mural?
How many signs were there on the mural?
We had...
The ship.
After that, we had music, then we had build fortification and pushback impurity.
That's four.
Well, goddamn!
Now I really don't know.
Let's look for something that involves five.
One, two, three, four, five... That's six.
This is also four, five, six.
This is six, this is one, two, three, four, five.
This is seven.
Don't think that's related.
Oh, man.
Now I'm really confused.
I think... I mean, obviously...
It's gotta have something to do with the book in here.
This has to be the puzzle to the bells, right?
So I gotta figure something out with this book.
Let's just try this order.
Duty, sun, moon chosen, but wait.
Chosen represents... the music.
Now, again, there's only four here.
And there's five things to adjust.
Oh, man.
Okay, you know what?
It's been an hour anyway.
I'm gonna take a break here.
And I'll be lost next time.
So thanks for watching.
Bye-bye.